This is
an
awesome treasure
hidden at the end of the sea,
and anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious point's our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there.
No regrets.
Every tear that we pride only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
Rubber?
It doesn't conduct electricity.
And so that means Enoru
can't hurt a rubber person.
Go, Luffy.
Stop him!
You you're no mere mortal what are you
me i'm luffy a pirate and a rubber man?
What i see rubber doesn't exist in
skypea he doesn't know what it is!
That lightning of yours won't work on me.
Mandala
Gum-Gum
Spear
Luffy!
Don't push your luck.
Lightning can cause far more
than just electric shocks.
But I don't have to tell
you that, Rubberman.
You found out the hard way.
I'm gonna have to do better than that!
I see he's got that weird ability
to predict my moves. Damn it!
Just what is this rubber?
Now hold on!
This rubber man!
He's a Paramecia!
Even they have weaknesses!
Gloom paddling.
I'm on a bit of a schedule,
so I don't have time to play.
He...
he's changing his staff into a blade!
Think of it as lightning in solid form!
As I thought, slashing attacks
are your weakness! Yeah!
Don't tell him that!
Gum-gum-godlich!
Where'd he go?
Murphy, behind you!
It can move right through the gold?
You may be immune to lightning,
but not to electric heat, it seems.
Oh, God!
You blasphemous brat!
All right, come run!
Get me!
It's not as though you
grew more arms, idiot.
Loopy!
Sightseeing on Sky Island.
You Blue Sea people certainly
picked a bad time to visit.
I am this land's god.
I can do anything my will desires.
I've long dreamed of
creating an ideal world.
This dream will become a reality, and
I won't let anyone stand in my way.
Least of all, some wealth
from the Blue Sea world.
Now, where were we?
Oh, yes, how could I forget?
You were going to watch this land die.
No, you can't!
Max, 200 million volts, party!
Oh, horsey bird, what are we going to do?
It's moving!
Luffy!
Mommy!
Behold, Maxim!
The ark that will take
me to endless birth,
to the sacred land
without end that I desire.
Rise, Maxim, rise!
It's flying.
This is bad.
Luffy, hurry up and stop Eneru.
Wait a minute, this
arc's powered by Eneru.
So if he's defeated,
it'll crash with us on it.
But if he's gone, the Sky
Island's gonna be destroyed?
And if we stay here and do nothing, we'll
be taken to some land far away within Aru!
Oh, I don't like our options!
No matter what happens, we still lose!
What are we gonna do, Luffy?
I'm really scared!
Don't be.
Just calm down.
Calm down? But how? How?!
You sail with the crew of the
future King of the Pirates.
So wipe that frown off, alright?
King of the Pirates?
And what domain does he lord over?
He's the King of the Seas,
the greatest king of all!
Hmph, so you say.
But we'll soon learn if
that's true, won't we?
Here, look! The ship!
It's stopped!
It's stuck in the berth!
It can't go any higher!
But look!
It's scraping away!
It's only a matter of time
before it breaks through!
No, we can't!
We'll get in his way!
He may be from the Blue Sea World,
but Luffy's still a warrior!
A warrior's duel is sacred!
You should never interfere in it!
The circuit to this
arc's ultimate function
has been initiated and
is now running at full
capacity it has a name it's called death
pia the despair that
will destroy this world?
What is that?
Chief, come quick!
Something's happening in
the sky over Upper Yard!
What is it?
It just suddenly got dark.
I've never seen the skies over
this island look like that.
Strange. What could it be?
Do you think something bad
happened to Wiper and the Warriors?
I hope not,
but I, too, have never seen such dark
clouds in the sky of the White White Sea.
That's right, thunderclouds.
Using my energy, Death Pier forces
extremely turbulent air currents together,
which produce those lovely thunderclouds
you see billowing out right now.
Thunderclouds?
Soon they will envelop all
of Skypiea in darkness.
Inside them, energy will continue to build
until it's reached its absolute peak.
And then, on my signal, they will
unleash thunderbolts of such magnitude!
That every trace of this
land will be obliterated.
Allow me to demonstrate.
That came from Upper Yard.
Get to the ships.
Everyone keep calm.
Don't panic.
Get on a ship and head for Cloud End.
Damn you.
I just tease the Angels a little but
after all that is my right so being a
god makes it okay to destroy everything
of course everything here is mine for
for the taking, their land, their lives.
Speaking of which, I'll continue
celebrating by taking yours.
This spear's been highly charged.
Damn it,
how, how can I defeat a guy
who can predict my moves?
Yeah.
Come, come!
Daze.
What are you doing? Hey!
He's dodging the attacks unconsciously
and just relying on his reflexes.
It's almost like he's a
blade of grass that sways
back and forth in the wind
instead of opposing it.
He's not thinking.
That's why Enoru can't predict his moves.
But if I switch my brain off
then I can't attack him
Don't stop now Gotta get my
hands on him somehow Come on
think there's gotta be a way
That's it
GUNGUN! GUNGUN! GUNGUN!
ENOUGH ON THE STUPID IDEAS!
I take it you're no fan of my Vonsular?
Are you?
That's to be expected, since
it's the basis of my power.
That place should work!
It doesn't matter what you try,
except for your immunity to lightning,
you're nothing but an
annoying, powerless mortal.
What?
Why attack the Ark?
I won't!
You're ignoring me and
attacking the ship instead?
It's no use.
You're even more foolish than you appear.
Ahhhh!
Of course!
The punches are ricocheting!
He's not consciously controlling them!
I'm not letting you get away again!
Goph Goph!
No, it's charging.
I have to escape.
He can't!
I...
I'm a god!
RIFLE!
Oh, no!
The ship's leaving the birds!
Yay!
What are we gonna do?
It's gonna fly away!
It worked!
You did it!
But, wait, the ship's taking off!
Oh no way he's getting back up you fools!
Is that the best you can do?
Make no mistake, boy!
When you're gone, the world will be mine!
And once again, everyone will fear
me who worship me and revere me I?
I am all-powerful!
In this world, filth like you
must learn the only truth.
By my hand, nothing is ever impossible!
For I am the almighty God!
Hey, look!
Up in the sky, something
floating over Upper Yard!
It's a... ship!
A flying ship? Impossible!
I've never heard of such a thing!
That's what made the sky turn dark?
God is on that ship!
Hey!
You gotta get out of here!
Board the ships!
Vessels are leaving Angel
Island by the hundreds!
What evil is this?
Those dark clouds are an ominous sign.
Look, someone is coming this way.
Shandora!
Take heed!
Ready your ships and evacuate!
The Sky Islands are doomed!
They're what?
You have to escape!
To the sea!
Not the blue sea.
Look hard rubber boy on
a falling islands despair?
Skypiea will be destroyed.
The angel's lives extinguished.
No one can stop me.
Not even you.
Wanna bet? No.
The golden wall!
No you don't!
Hey!
He melted it like butter!
He didn't out!
What's the matter, Rubber Man?
Don't you like the way I've even the odds?
I've simply taken the fight out of you.
You see,
I'm honestly not sure I could
take another hit from you.
Therefore, I think it best.
if we sever ties.
But in honor of the spirited
effort you've put forth,
take this gold bobble as a parting gift!
Once I'm finally rid of you,
this world will be mine again.
Just as it was before and not
a soul in the world can defeat
me not a soul in the world
you're an idiot even if I can't
defeat you back in the blue sea
there are tons more fighters
who can put you in your place
someone like you could Never!
You talk too much, boy.
Now fall!
Fall along with the Sky Island!
You won't win! Ah!
No!
Luffy.
You've been around!
Horsy Bird, look!
That's Luffy!
He's falling!
Oh no!
Aissa and Pierre!
Aissa.
So that sly little voice
I've been hearing has a name.
Find me, you coward!
Luffy!
We're coming to save you!
I tire of this time to die.
God's judgment?
Luffy!
I'm not here!
For all my strength, he hurt me.
Yet, here I stand, the victor.
It's enormous.
So this is the Ark the Divine
Squad was forced to build.
Right here, on the northeastern
edge of the island.
After the others get the gold, this is
where we're all supposed to meet up.
And once all of you are together again,
you're planning to escape, right?
As long as we have the treasure,
I'm not going anywhere without it.
Nami...
They're heading northeast towards the
seashore, no doubt returning to their ship.
The smartest thing to do right now is go
on ahead and wait for them to show up.
After all, they'll need me to
guide them back to the Blue Sea.
I'm their best chance
to escape the island.
But I have to get to the
Going Merry, and fast!
Nami.
You smell nice.
No!
It's not fair!
One minute I'm dreaming,
the next I'm in a nightmare!
Wait, hold on.
Nami!
What...
what is that?
Bellarine, Bellarine,
Bellarine, Bellarine, Bellarine!
Nami!
She's in trouble!
Hey, Usopp! Wake up!
This is no time to be in bed, you idiot!
What is it?
What's wrong?
Never mind that. Let's go.
Go where?
Where do you think to rescue Nami?
Rescue, huh?
Oh, yeah!
It's all coming back to me!
I remember everything!
No...
God came!
Oh, nice, I angered God.
Would you relax?
He's long gone by now.
This morning and say, how
can I get myself smooted?
It's Nami who's in trouble.
She's the one who got kidnapped!
Nami?
How could we have been so stupid?
This is all our fault!
She's too cute for this!
Okay, so he took her.
But where to?
There! Huh?
It... big...
big ship... lying!
Though I only saw her for a second,
I'm sure it was Nami on that ship.
And while I may not know
what dangers lie ahead,
at least she's not wearing
that T-shirt anymore.
Again? With a t-shirt? Focus!
I feel like I'm missing something here.
Where are Conis, Weird
Night, and the others?
I don't know, but we have to hurry.
Hey, Sanji, where you going?
To that ship, where else? Say what?
Run faster or we'll lose him.
My love needs us.
Yeah, so, um, if I'm following
you, does that mean I'm going to?
Of course!
I need your help to get on board.
You still have that rope
you shoot out of your belly.
My Usafa!
Oh, sure, I'll let you use
it while I wait down here.
Just hurry up, you coward!
Can it, moron!
We don't have any more time to waste!
I'm coming for you,
Nami, my beautiful swan!
Swan!
Now that the Archmaxim is activated,
nothing can save this nation
from its inevitable destruction.
What's wrong?
You're lucky to have made it this far.
Abandon all thoughts of
your incompetent playmates
and embrace the glorious
future I've given you.
Yeah, thanks.
You're a swell guy.
But one thing's more precious than gold.
It's a treasure called friendship.
We're gonna get some gold, yeah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
And treasure! Tomorrow!
What good is owning the world's
wealth without friends to share it?
This island is filled with riches
I'd love to get my hands on.
But sacrificing my friends and enduring
your ego is too steep a price to pay.
So your treasure it's yours I don't
want it really you don't want anything?
Not even your life!
Calm down, Sue.
Tell me what happened.
But wait, neither Sanji nor Usopp
are in any shape to be moving around.
Why aren't they here?
Where did they go?
Come on, tell me.
Sanji woke up and then
he woke up Usopp and
they both ran and jumped
up to the...the ship?
You're sure?
But they're not fully healed.
Oh, look at this place.
It's a mess.
God of the White Sea or not, if he lays
a finger on Nami, I'll be his personal
Luffy, I need to borrow
some of your courage.
from home, gazing not at the sky.
You are just like the moon.
You'll never change as
you're climbing to the night.
But your reflection wanes.
Then you disappear, fading so silently.
Stay as you are.
Don't move your way.
Let these words guide you.
Don't ever look back.
Don't give up on your dreams.
Their endless nights, they come to you.
Again and again.
Until you see the journey through.
You may not return.
I hope that you learn.
To put your past behind.
And just keep moving on.